Guide to the Labor Publications and Printed Material Collection, "1861-2011 IBT0001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Miscellaneous Labor, 1861-2010; Series 3; 1 Linear Feet
  - Wal-Mart: Rolling Back Workers' Wages, Rights, And The American Dream, 2005; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Water Front Supercargo by Tom Murray, 1980; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - What's Next for Textile Workers by Emanuel Blum and Joseph Figueiredo, 1948; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - What Organized Labor Expects of Management by George Meany, 1955; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Why...Time Study, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Woman's Place is at the Typewriter: the Feminization of the Clerical Labor Force by Margery Davies, 1974 July-August; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Working in Early Rhode Island by Edwin C. Brown, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Workmen's Earnings, Strikes, and Savings by Samuel Smiles, 1861; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - You Ain't Never Hear About Any Struggles: Oral History in the Classroom by Kristine Feichtinger, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Young + Old = Union Power by Union Communication Services, 2010; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Your Government by Machinists Non-Partisan Political League, 1952; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - The 1936-39 Revolt in Palestine by Ghassan Kanafani, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Strike: The Labor Relations Game, Undated; Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    This is a board game enclosed in a tube. The game notes that it is for 2-4 players ages 12 and up. It was produced by the Kamber Group of Washington, D.C.
  - Poor Richard Almanack: Official Organ of the Poor Richard Club, March 1941; Series 3 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 1)
- Reprints, 1910-1984; Series 4; 1 Linear Feet
  - American Labor's Continuing Involvement in World Affairs by Roy Godson, 1975; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - American Trade Unionism Past and Present by Lloyd Ulman, 1961; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - A Brief History of U.S. Asian Labor by Karl Yoneda, 1976 September; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Back to Normalcy: A Study of American Industrial and Social Problems by W. Everett Brockman, 1921; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Black Labor As A Swing Factor in South Africa's Evolution by Roy Godson, 1979; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The Bulletin of the University of Wisconsin: the Knights of St. Crispin, 1867-1874 by Don D. Lescohier, 1910 July; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "Cohesion and Disunity in the ICFTU: the 1965 Amsterdam Congress," by John P. Windmuller, April 1966; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Collective Bargaining and Idustrial Efficiency by Lloyd Ulman, 1968; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Collective Bargaining in the Motion Picture Industry by Hugh Lovell and Tasile Carter, 1955; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Collective Bargaining in the Nonferrous Metals Industry bu Vernon H. Jensen, 1955; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Corruption and Racketeering in the Labor Movement by Philip Taft, 1970; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Craft Unionusm Revisited: The Case of the Waitress Locals by Dorothy Sue Cobble, undated; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The Crisis in American Unionism bu Edwin E. Witte, 1958-1959; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Democracy in the Labor Movement by Joel Seidman, 1969; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - The Expanding Role of Government and Labor in the American Economy by Waldo E. Fisher, 1950 January 30; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Extracurricular Activities of the McClellan Committee by Paul Jacobs, 1963; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - The Foriegn Policy Conflict in American Labor by John P. Windmuller, June 167; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - The Head-Fixing Industry by John Keracher, 1955; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Histoire Du Mouvement Syndical Ouest-Africain D'expression Francaise par Lambert Bovy, Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Hoffa's Acquisition of Industrial Power by Ralph James and Estelle James, 1963; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hoffa's Impact on Teamster Wages by Ralph James and Estelle James, 1964; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hoffa's Leverage Techniques in Bargaining by Ralph James and Estelle James, 1964; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - ICFTU After Ten Years: Problems and Perspectives, by John P. Windmuller, January 1961; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Ideologies and Industrial Conflict and Philip Taft, undated; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Industrial Price Policies by the Bookings Institute, 1938; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Industrial Relations in the Construction Industry by Gordon W. Bertram and Sherman J. Maisel, 1955; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Internal Affairs of Unions and the Taft-Hartley Act by Philip Taft, 1958 April; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Internal Characteristics of American Unionism by Philip Taft, 1951 March; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - International Trade Union Organizations: Structures, Functions, and Limitations by John P. Windmuller, 1967; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Jurisdictional Disputes Resulting From Structural Differences in American Trade Unions by Solomon Blum, 1913 September 27; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Labor: A Partner in American Foreign Policy? by John P. Windmuller, November 1963; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Leadership and Administration in the ICFTU: A new Phase of Development by John P. Windmuller, 1961; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - The Ludlow Massacre by Alvin R. Sunseri, undated; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Minimum Wages: Issues and Evidence by Finis Welch, 1978; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Nonfactory Unionism and Labor Relations by Van Dusen Kennedy, 1955; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Political Directions for Labor by Kim Moody, 1979 September; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Professor Perlman's Ideas and Activities by Phlip Taft, undated; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Public Policy and Discrimination in Apprenticeship by George Strauss and Sidney Ingerman, 1965; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Purge of the Trotskyites from the Teamsters by Ralph James and Estelle James, 1966; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rediscovering American Labor by Penn Kemble, 1971 April; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Reflections on the Present of the Labor Movement, undated; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Reflections on Selig Perlman as a Teacher and Writer by Philip Taft, 1976 January; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - A Rereading of Selig Perman's A Theory of the Labor Movement by Philip Taft, 1950 October; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - The Rise of Organized Labor by Donald Oliver and Fred M. Newmann, 1973-1974; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The Shop Steward and His Job from John J. Glynn, 1955 February 21; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Short History of Chicano Workers by Lorenzo Torrez, 1973 October - November; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The Subversion of Collective Bargaining by Danile Bell, 1960 March; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - The Teamsters and NLRB Representation Elections, 1962-1963 by Walter Fogel, 1965; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Union Myopia and the Taxation of Capial by Dwight R. Lee, 1984 December; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - The Unionization of the American Steel Industry by Walter Galenson, 1956; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Unions in the Building Trades by George Strauss, 1958 June; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - The Unlicesnsed Seafaring Unions by Philip Taft, 1950 January; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Uprising by and For Postal Workers, 1974 November; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Violence in American Labor Disputes, 1966 March; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The Workers in the Dawn: Labor Lore bu Archie Green, 1969 July 7; Series 4; 1 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Union Publications, 1899-2013; Series 5; 6.25 Linear Feet
  Arranged alphabetically. Note: starting with Box 17, the order of this series restarts. Note:starting with Box 19, the order of this series restarts Note:starting with Box 25, the order of this series restarts Note: starting with Box 33, the order restarts
  - Abolition of the Inquisitorial Committees of Congress, 1957; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Action Against Jim Crow by United Packinghouse Workers of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - A Dangerous Combination, 1960s; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - The AFL-CIO Case for Repeal of 14(b) by George Meany, 1965; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO Centennial Anthology by AFL-CIO, 1981November; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO Films, 1979; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Manual for Shop Stewards, 1958; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Manual For Shop Stewards, April 1985; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO: Report of the Executive Council, 7 December 1967; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO Steward's Manual, 1999; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO Resolutions on Collective Bargaining and Related Issues by American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organization, 1955 December; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO Resolutions on Social Security Welfare and Related Issues by American Federation on Labor and Congress of Inustrial Organizations, 1955 December; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Airline Teamsters Journal, Fall 2007; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - ALA: "to find answers to urgent problems of our society", 1968; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - ALA: Founding Conference, 26-27 May 1969; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - A Look At The Facts On Right To Work Laws, 1953-1962; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - All-African Peoples' Conference-Tunis, January 1960; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - All-African Trade Union Federation, Revolutionary Journal of the AATUF-Volume 1, Number 4, January 1966; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - American Federation Of Labor and Congress Of Industrial Organizations, 9 November 1973; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - American Labor and the American Spirit, 1954; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - American Labor History Told by Those Who Lived It, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - American Labor Looks at The World, 1954; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The American Labor Movement, 1962; Series 7 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Application for Membership and/or Increase in Membership Benefits by Brotherhood's Relief and Compensation Fund, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Apprentice Indenture by Graphic Arts International Union, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Athene In Steeltown, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Arise Chicago Newsletter, 2012 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - An Argument For Co-Operative Loan Associations, June 1911; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Arsenal of Facts, 1938-1939; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Back the Team by Joint Council of the Teamsters No. 42, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers International Union and the Partnership Agreements, 1994; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers International Union, 23 Janaury 1986; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Basic Principles: Aggressive Struggle and Rank and File Control by United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Battle Stations for Peace by National Council of the National Maritime Union, 1946 March; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Beyond the Law: The Strikebreaking Industry in Ontario by Brennan Waldie and associates, 1928 August 27; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Bill Cloud International Typography Union Biography, Undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Bill of Rights for the Undocumented Worker by International Coordinating Committee, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - The Birth of a Union Local: The History of UAW Local 674, Norwood, Ohio 1933-1940 by John G. Kruchko, 1972 August; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Black Workers and the American Labor Movement by Thomas R. Brooks, 1971; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Brief History of the United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union (AFL-CIO, CFC) by United Cement, Lime, and Gypsum Workers International Union (AFL-CIO,CFC), undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Breve Histoire Du Mouvement Syndical International, 1962-1963; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen: A Brief Sketch of Its History, Functions, and Accomplishments by Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Cleveland 13 Ohio, 1953; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Black Gang News vol. 1 no. 20, 1936 August 27; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Bloody Thursday 50th Anniversary by ILWU, 1984; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Blue Ridge the History of our Struggle Against Levi-Streuss, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Brookwood A School For Progressive Labor Education, 1932-1933; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - The Builder: News from the Building and Construction Trade Department, AFL-CIO, 2004; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Building a Strong Teamsters Union on a Foundation of Reform, 1996 June; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Building the Local Union, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Building Trades Directory of Rhode Island by Providence Building Trades Council, 1957 February; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - By-Laws for Local Unions by United Steelworkers of America, 1962 November 9; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - By Our Own Hands - United Brotherhood of Carpenters Membership Kit, Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Camouflage - The Myth of "Labor Monopoly", June 1960; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Careers in Sheet Metal, 1985; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - The Case For Federal Job Standards, December 1972; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - The Case for the Union Shop by Industrial Union Department (AFL-CIO), undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Change to Win, 27 September 2005; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Challenges for Apprenticeship and Vocational Training in the 1990s: German and American Perspectives, 1992; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - The Changing Proile of Black Workers, April 1974; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - The Changing Situation Of Workers and Their Unions, February 1985; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Changing Work: A Union Guide to Workplace Change, 1994; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - The Changing World Of Multinationals, September 1974; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - The Check Off by National Maritime Union, 1943 August; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Child-Labor Provisions of the Fair Labor Standards Act, January 1967; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Chow Time and Real Milk! by the National Maritime Union, 1945 June 1; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Civil Rights, 1960s; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - CIO 1935-1955 Industrial Democracy in Action by Industrial Union Department, American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1955 December 1; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - The CIO Crusade by John Lewis, 1937 October; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - CIO's 1940 Legislative Program for Jobs, Security and Peace by Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1940 January; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - CIO and Labor Unity by Congress of Industrial Organizations, undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - CIO's Program for Latin America by CIO Department of Education and Research, 1950 October; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - CIO Re-employment Plan by Philip Murray, 1945; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Citizenship for Harry Bridges Production Soldier by Leo Huberman, 1942 November; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cobblestone - The Mill Girls From Farm to Factory, March 2001; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Collective Bargaining - Democracy on the Job, July 1965; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - College Costs Squeeze the Worker Out, December 1972; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - The Colonial Strike by Jim Bollen, A Small Strike by John Emery Mitchell and Steve Miller, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - The Coming Ship Subsiding Scandal by William L. Standard, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Common Action in Common Interest-WTFU-AATUF, March 1969; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Compulsory Arbitration, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Congres General de L'Union Generale des Travailleurs' de L'Afrique Noire-Sekou Toure, 1959; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Constitutional and By-Laws of the International Brotherhood of Police Officers, 1974 October 27; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the National Association of Government Employees, 1974 October 27; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - The Constitution and Rules of Order of the Iron Molders' Union of North America, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Constitution of the Boot and Shoe Workers Union by Boot and Shoe Workers Union, 1939 June 22; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cooperating For The Future, 1987; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Corporate Crime Comics, 1970s; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Candadian Labour and Politics by Clifford A. Scotton, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cry for Justice by Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1972; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Cultural Correspondence, 1978; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Daily Proceedings of the Twelfth Constitutional Convention of the Congress of Indsutrial Organizations, 1950 November 20; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Decline of the AFL-CIO, 30 August 1962; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - The Decline of the AFL-CIO, 30 August 1962; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Dedication of the Headquarters Building, 1955; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Defend and Strengthen African American Workers by Black Workers for Justice, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - A Democratic Institution by William Green, 1952 April; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Detroit Auto Uprising 1973, Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Directory of I.S. and E.U. Union Label Dies from the Office of the Secretary-Treasurer I.S. and E.U., 1958; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Discours D'Ouverture du President Ahmed Sekou Toure-12eme Session de la Conference des Ministres Africains du Travail, 1974; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Do You Have a Complaint for a Grievance by the United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO-CLC, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Do You Have a Complaint or a Grievance? by the United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO-CLC, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Do You Know that...by the National Maritime Union, 1943 September; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Economic Development- A Union Guide to the High Road, 1998; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Draft Constitution for the New, Merged Labor Organization, 1955 May 2; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Economic Squeeze On The Worker, 1974, Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - The Economy in 1967 by Walter P. Reuther, 1967 February 20; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Education and Training for the Changing Workplace, 1995; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Education for What? The New Office Economy Technical Report, 1998; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Electing Union Officers, February 1967; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Employees Retirement Plan National Metal Trades Association, 15 November 1959; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Engineering and Inspection Division The Travelers Hartford, Connecticut, Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Equal Rights for the AFL-CIO Program by American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1970 May; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - An Evening with Labor by the Metropolitan Washington Council AFL-CIO, 2001 March 17; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Excerpts from the General Laws of the Upholsterers' International Union of North America A.F.ofL., undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Explosion in Family Living Costs, November 1974; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Facts You Should know About Your Employment Security Program, 1 June 1949; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The False Promise:Professionalism in Nursing by Boston Nurses Group, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Farmworkers Build Thier Union Si Se Puede! by Salinas Citizens Committee in Defense of Farmworkers, 1973 July; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Fascism - Speech of Hon. William E. Borah, 6 May 1937; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Feeding the Iron Hog: The Life and Work of a Locamotive Fireman bu the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1927; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - The Fight For Economic Justice by CIO Organizing Committee, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Films from Labor and How to Use Them by CIO Film Division, Department of Educational Research, 1950 November; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Flight Attendant Milestones: 50 Years of CALFAA and CUPE, 1998; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Food Prices: A Policy Failure, August 1973; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - From the men who man the ships to the men who man the guns, January 1945; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - From The Men and Women Who Man the Ships to Mr. and Mrs. America U.S.A., 10 June 1948; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - The First Labor Day Parade, 16 September 1882; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - For A New Workers Social Contract by Lynn R. Williams, 1984 June 7; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - For URCLPNA-CIO Stewards by CIO Department of Education and Research, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Forge Negro-Labor Unity for Peace and Jobs by Paul Roberson, 1950 August; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Free Trade Unions in Africa-Fourth Regional Conference of the I.C.F.T.U., April 1964; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Free Trade Unions in the Fight for African Freedom by John Riddell, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - The Forward March of American Labor by the League for Industrial Democracy, 1945; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - From the Kitchen of Congress by the Education Department of the National Maritime Union, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Gearing Money Policy To Economic Growth, May 1964; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - George Meany by the AFL-CIO American Federationist, 1979 December; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - The George Meany Center For Labor Studies, 1992-1993; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - George Meany Center For Labor Studies Antioch University College Degree Program - Student Handbook, Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - George Meany The Making of A Freedom Fighter, 16 November 1979; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Getting Along With People by Eugene J. Benge, 1951; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Ghana Workers' Bulletin-United Brotherhood of Workers, Vol.1, No.1, January 7, 1967; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Green Paper- Re-imagining Work, 2015; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Group Insurance Plan by the UIU Health and Welfare Fund, 1954 November 1; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Group Insurance Plan Policy 22344-03 by the UIU Health and Welfare Fund, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Guide Des Delegues-2 Congres, Confederation Syndicale Africaine, Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Half a Million Forgotten People: The Story of the Cotton Textile Workers by the Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1944; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Hamilton Watch Timebook, 1929 March 13; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hamilton Watch Timebook, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Handbook on Seamen's Unemployment Insurance by National Maritime Union of America, CIO, 1947 August; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Handling Grievances: A Handbook for Committeemen of Local Lodges of S.W.O.C. by the Workers Organizing Committee, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Health of the Worker How To Safeguard It, 1924; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Healthy Soil - Healthy People by the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1948; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 7)